JARRISON CANO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



300 612 38 86

Medellín, Colombia

✓ Jarrison.cano@hotmail.com

in Jarrison Cano | LinkedIn

Jarrison Cano | GitHub

Profile

Hello, I'm Jarrison Cano, I'm currently 19 years old, I live in Medellin, Colombia and I'm studying a technology in design and web development at the Technological University of Antioquia. I have experience working as Software developer with technologies such as: React Js, React Native and TypeScript. I am actively on GitHub developing and collaborating with the community.

I am a person who likes challenges, continuous learning and trying on a daily basis to grow personally and professionally. I am a lover of developing with technologies focused on JavaScript and sharing my knowledge with others. I am passionate about Formula 1 and I like to practice sports, especially running and cycling.

LANGUAGES

✓ English: Intermediate

✓ Spanish: Native

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance.

Autónomo. Ene 2020 – Ago 2021.

Desarrollador de software.

Logística y Transporte Atalaya S.A.S. Ago 2021 – Actualidad.

SKILLS

JavaScript Styled Components

React Js Style jsx

Next Js Scss

TypeScript Motion
Graph-QL ChakraUI
Node Js (Express) Bootstrap

Mongo DB

SQL Server

EDUCATION

Bachiller Técnico.

Colegio Parroquial Emaús. Ene. 2008 - Nov 2019

Tecnología en Diseño Y Desarrollo Web.

Tecnológico de Antioquia. Ene. 2020 - Actualmente

Cursos, Bootcamps.

Código Facilito. Platzi, FreCodeCamp, EDteam, etc.